RG 002:025, Banks Committee
Connecticut State Library
Banks Committee records
1980-1997
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Banks
1.5 cubic feet
The Banks Committee has cognizance of all matters relating to banks, savings banks, bank and trust companies, savings and loan associations, credit unions, the supervision of the sale of securities, fraternal benefit societies and all legislation dealing with secured and unsecured lending. Consists of meeting documents including notices, agendas, minutes, attendance, and roll calls; bill books, and correspondence.
RG002_025_BANK
1999-061
Historical Note
The Banks Committee has cognizance of all matters relating to banks, savings banks, bank and trust companies, savings and loan associations, credit unions, the supervision of the sale of securities, fraternal benefit societies and all legislation dealing with secured and unsecured lending.
Scope and Content
The records include meeting documents for most years. These consist of notices, agendas, minutes, roll call votes, and attendance. Session reports may consist of roll call attendance and vote records for a session, list of bills considered to be most important by the committee, lists of bills that received a Joint Favorable report by the committee, and vote sheets.
Arrangement
Arranged by year.
Related Material
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Banks and banking -- Government policy -- Connecticut; Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Banks -- Records and correspondence
Document Types:
Agendas (administrative records); Correspondence; Minutes (administrative records); Statutes
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1980-1997
  - 1980
    - Meeting documents, 1980 February - March (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1982
    - Banking Dept. proposals, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1983
    - Meeting documents, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bill book, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1984
    - Bill book, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Legislative proposals, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Meeting documents, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - News clippings, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Reference material, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Testimonies, 1984 February 29 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1985
    - Bill book, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - H.B. 7653 - Technical Revisions to the General Statutes Relating to Credit Unions, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Meeting documents, 1985 January - February (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Meeting documents, 1985 March - May (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Meeting documents, 1985 September - October (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Membership, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Subcommittee A - Interstate Banking, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Subcommittee B - Home Office Protection, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Subcommittee D - Consumer Issues, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1986
    - Bill book, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Meeting documents, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Reference material, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1987
    - Bill book, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - HB 6435 - An Act Concerning the Creation of Durable Power of Attorney Bank Accounts, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - HB 7108 - The Priority of Claims Against State-Chartered Depository Institutions in Receivership, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Meeting documents, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Session reports, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Financial Planning Study Committee - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Financial Planning Study Committee - Meeting documents, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Financial Plannning Study Committee - Membership, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1988
    - Bill book, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Meeting documents, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Membership, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 1989
    - Bill book, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Meeting documents, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Transcript, 1989 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 1990
    - Bill book, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Interstate banking, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Meeting documents, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Membership, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 1991
    - Bills, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Meeting documents, 1991 January - February (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Meeting documents, 1991 March - May (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Membership, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Session reports, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 1992
    - Bill book, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HB 5402 - An Act Concerning the Incorporation of Aetna Fiduciary Services, Inc. and Cigna Fiduciary Services, Inc., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Meeting documents, 1992 January - February (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Membership, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Session reports, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1994
    - Bank survey fee, 1994 August (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Meeting documents, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Requests to raise bills, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Session reports, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1995
    - Bill book, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Meeting documents, 1995 February 16, March 4 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Session reports, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1997
    - Meeting documents, 1997 March 20, April 11 (Box 2, Folder 13)